chatbazaar.com 2015-12-07

# Free Chat rooms, Chatting, UK US London Dating Chat - Privacy Policy : www.chatbazaar.com

### Disclaimer and Terms of Use

By accessing any part of chatbazaar.com you agree to this "Agreement" in full whether you register or not with chatbazaar.com. Check Disclaimer and Terms of use for futher detail.

### About Us

Chatbazaar.com is an online chat social networking service provider which allows members to chat live and create unique personal profile where they can share their interest and personal detail including country, city, hometown, age, picture and more. Visitors/Members can view other members profiles. To identify members and to enable them connect/communicate.

Chatbazaar.com cares deeply about online privacy If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at privacy @ chatbazaar.com.

### Information collection and Use

Chatbazaar.com collects user information during registration information such as full name, date of birth, gender, country, city , home town and email to authenticate user and send notification and updates relating to chatbazaar.com's services.  
Chatbazaar.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.

### Credit card details, Customer details and Use

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. 

### Google Adverts

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

### Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members

Chatbazaar.com members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Chatbazaar.com stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations Chatbazaar.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations from Chatbazaar.com may contact Chatbazaar.com to request the removal of their information from our database.

### Cookies

Chatbazaar.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from Chatbazaar.com in order to use most functions on the site Please note that Chatbazaar.com allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Chatbazaar.com Privacy Policy.

### Links

Chatbazaar.com contains links to sites. Chatbazaar.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Chatbazaar.com.

### Chat Rooms, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to chat rooms, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

### Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

Chatbazaar.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.

### Email

We may send members new promotions and update regarding Chatbazaar.com's services.

### Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by Chatbazaar.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Chatbazaar.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Security

Chatbazaar.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords Chatbazaar.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on Chatbazaar.com, please contact us a privacy @ Chatbazaar.com

### Sharing and Disclosure of Information Chatbazaar.com Collects

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Chatbazaar.com will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Chatbazaar.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Chatbazaar.com Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Chatbazaar.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Chatbazaar.com or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: privacy @ Chatbazaar.com
